<Mod title="The Hand (W.I.P)" gameVersion="109" author="Sho" description="Reworking everything from scratch. Expect chaos. ETA: 1 month (or whenever I stop suffering).

Trying to learn Blender so i can add new guns, new helmets, armors, and new toys for yalll...maybe go play another mod while i&apos;m cooking this 🥲I&apos;m sorry

26/04/2025: Sorry for a crappy update, but i ran out of time and won&apos;t able to fully focus on this thing anymore.
Here&apos;s an &quot;temporary&quot; update for new items. I gotta admit that since i mod this game, i started to hate this game, lol,  there&apos;s just so many bull shit that limits my ideas A LOT, and i mean A LOT. The most creative things i can do is probably with the grenades, lol. Outside of that, i HATE this shit and how crappy this mod had became. Sorry, the scope went out of control too fast.
Anyway, please create a new squad, sorry, its why i keep every items cost at 0 (For now)
There&apos;s still a lot of unused assets...which contains some very cool looking helmet...but what would i do with only a fucking helmet and no suitable armor??? fuck the mod architecture, it sucks, i need to use 3dsmax which i have 0 experience in to fucking create one, so, sorry, but i will revisit these in the future
I will admit that i don&apos;t have time to properly test shits out before update, that&apos;s why, once again, i&apos;m sorry, but if anything bugs you or seems out of place, please yell at me.
There&apos;s too many thing to talk about, but here&apos;s my updated roadmap when i return to this shit in the future.

0.5(current version): Equipment updates...yeah, you saw it, new shits, but i don&apos;t have time to refine those shits yet.
0.6: Gun updates, new sounds, new models if possible, new effects for guns, and rework old guns so they have up-to-date styles.
0.7:QOL update, i will polish the things above, add proper descriptions, proper balance and shits, i will also rework doctrine to lock in a suitable playstyle for the squad. (current loadouts and shits are too bloated, and have a lot of unnessary shits, non-balance and all)
0.8:Visual update, this is gonna be a tough one, since i&apos;m still stuck with 3dsmax...but i&apos;m thinking about giving 2-3 new models for the squads, 1 male 1 female armors/uniforms. and 1 for the expendable units, I will try to update voicelines too if i can find some good pack, or....well...nope i guess?
0.9:lore and campaign update, this probably will be the easiest one since i like to do these shits more than the other aspects, i like writing, but fuck me i don&apos;t have time 😭 i hate my life, i hate myself. Anyway, i will create 2 campaign, 1 with just a normal scary themed ToD, the other will have its own storyline where i try to recreate a mission for the NTF themselves. If i suceed in adding new models with animations from 0.8 update, i will add new enemies for these too....damn i have a lot of assets but 0 talents.
1.0: Release? After this i will continue to write as its my hobby, and of course, refining, adding missing shits to the game, balancing, blah blah...oh my god imma kill myself.
Lastly, if anyone want to help me(I need help, seriously), please contact me, working on this shit alone is killing my sanity. I don&apos;t even know what is going on inside my mod right now.

Blah blah blah, bye bye guys,  imma study now, i have a class in 1 hour

If you wanna yell at me for whatever reasons, DM me on Discord: [b]Sho#3765[/b] – I’m online very frequently.
" changeNotes="Quick update to fix Katana missing texture and wrong portraits" languageMod="" tags="Playable Units,Equipment" ugcId="3447618979"/>
